[suspenseful music playing]
[officer 1] Police! Get down!
Nobody move! Let me see your hands!
[officer 2] Hands on your head!
- [gunshots]
- [officer 3] Get down. get down!
[officer 1] Automatic weapon!
- [officer 3] Go. go!
- [officer 1] Hands on your head!
- [officer 1] Target down.
- [officer 2] Stay down!
[woman on comm] Target neutralized.
- [knocking on door]
- [officer 1] Police!
[officer 2] Police. open up!
- Police. open up!
- [knocking on door]
[Tanya] Explosive set. Ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
[music ends]
[indistinct chatter]
[Djibril] Nice work. man.
[Valère] "Valère in position!"
I get the go. and boom!
They said there's someone
waiting for you at the gate.
Okay. Uh. Cédric. could you give me
something real to do in the next…
Listen. um. Max.
You're a good teammate. and I mean it.
I'm not bullshitting.
In a couple of weeks
they'll decide what's next for you.
I don't know what that is.
but we both know you're finished here.
My job is to make sure the section works
without you and David. okay?
So why would I want to include you. huh?
But take a break. Go see your visitor.
[helicopter whirring overhead]
[distant buzzing]
[lock beeps]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [ominous music playing]
[sighs]
ELITE FORCE
[poignant classical piano music playing]
[music continues]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[music stops]
[answering machine beeps]
Hey. this is Manon's voice mail.
If I didn't pick up…
I told her to leave her phone on.
She didn't leave it on.
I don't know if she's going
straight to school or if she's at Nina's.
Are they taking the bus?
Do they need a drive?
Let me look after Manon.
Stop worrying and go to work.
It'll give me the chance
to follow my dream
of becoming the world's
most accomplished stay-at-home father.
[chuckles]
Keep in mind. I can work on it
here in Paris. or in Hong Kong. same diff.
Singapore.
Hong Kong. Singapore. you decide.
[chuckles]
So. you got this?
Absolutely. piece of cake.
[tender music playing]
- Take your phone.
- Oh. right.
- Your coffee?
- Thanks.
Thanks. you're sweet.
I love you.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Your father had just joined the force
with David.
David hadn't met Jess yet.
We weren't even your age.
We were still kids.
Laurent was deployed
for four months in New Caledonia.
And because of my job. I couldn't go.
A while after he came back.
I noticed I was late.
I did a test. I was pregnant. with you.
We were overjoyed.
Our parents thought we were too young
but we didn't care.
The day you were born
was the happiest day of our lives.
[pensive music playing]
You were growing up
and we wanted to give you
a little brother. or a little sister.
We tried again.
For weeks and months. It didn't work.
We went to see a specialist.
and we learned the truth.
Laurent was unable to have children.
Up to then. I'd always thought
Laurent was your father.
Why are you telling me all this?
So I'll forgive you? Is that it?
So I say. "It's no big deal. Mom"?
I don't need your forgiveness.
Having you was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
- I won't apologize for that.
- But you lied to me. you…
You cheated on Dad.
With David?
Why didn't you tell me
the truth after he died?
Would it have helped you to know?
I just wanted to protect you. I…
Of course it would have helped me.
I have a father who's alive!
I had the right to know!
[music turns poignant]
I was the one
who kept David out of your life.
What?
Your father died
because David told him everything.
What right did he have
to see you after that?
Because of that one time. 25 years ago?
You stole my father from me.
don't you understand?
You had no fucking right!
[breathes shakily]
[alarm blaring]
[Max] Ah. fuck.
[Nathalie] Max!
Oh. shit…
[cell phone buzzing]
Yeah?
David. it's Valère.
Where's your daughter right now?
What is this?
Why are you asking about my daughter?
Her music school.
There's a hostage situation.
but we don't know who's inside.
[suspenseful music playing]
FRENCH ARMY
[pilot] Airborne on approach.
Target confirmed.
[officer] Sir. sir. you can't go through.
[police sirens blaring]
Okay. it's fine.
[suspenseful music continues]
[sniper 1] Fox 1 in position.
[sniper 2] Fox 3 in position.
[drone whirring]
[officer] This is Delta 5.
we're at security.
Entrances have been rigged
with explosives.
Identification in progress.
[suspenseful music continues]
[pilot] Copy that.
We're maintaining position
above the target.
[sirens blaring distantly]
Check if the command post
has a list of hostages. okay?
- [Chloé] Okay.
- A quick briefing. everyone.
The van parked out front.
it's been there overnight.
- I'll check it out.
- Sure. go ahead.
So. listen up.
They arrived yesterday
and spent the night there.
They have assault weapons.
They're masked and prepared.
At 9:00 a.m. they started shooting.
Two people were wounded.
but they managed to escape.
Since then.
we've heard nothing from the terrorists.
We assume they're holed up
inside somewhere.
We've set up these three fire supports.
All on the roof of the station. okay?
Have we identified the Oscars?
- We're expecting that any minute now.
- And where are we on tactical assault?
Nowhere yet. I have no visibility.
We have a 55 on the targets?
Fuck. Are we in contact
with them. at least?
They're not answering our calls.
They're well-prepared.
Thanks. David. I know what I'm doing.
Here are my concerns.
They have hostages.
but they haven't made any demands.
We don't know what they want.
but we know what we have to do.
Get your teams together
and be ready to move in. Let's do it.
[indistinct chatter]
- We're in contact with building security.
- Calling them now.
[Cédric] Okay. come on.
I need that hostage list.
Hang on. here it is.
- We're good. we got the list.
- [Cédric] Print it out. please.
[tense music playing]
I'm with them now.
We don't know if she's inside yet.
Okay. so what do you know?
Not a lot. actually.
They still haven't told me much.
But of course. as soon as I get something.
I'll let you know.
Okay. Maybe I should try Nina again.
I can't reach her either.
- Hold on.
- What is it?
[music darkens]
She's in there.
Huh?
[breathes shakily]
[gasps]
[sobs]
She's my baby.
Jess.
[Jess sobbing]
Jess. I'm gonna get her out.
I promise. You hear me?
[crying]
I promise you.
Call you back.
No. no. no. no. wait. wait!
- [crying]
- [call ends]
[phone clatters]
David!
What are you doing?
Thinking of going in alone?
Leave this to us.
We know what we're doing.
Oh. yeah?
Why haven't you formed
a tactical column already?
[Cédric] We don't know
how many terrorists there are.
They've rigged doors.
We don't know where to send in a column.
I didn't say send in a column.
I said you should form one!
If you send in a column at the last second
and you haven't formed one.
you lost 30 seconds.
We don't even know where they are!
We have no videos.
nobody's talked to them.
We have no clue what they want.
We're not ready.
Hey! I'm not an idiot. Manon's in there.
but you're not running things.
That's my job. okay?
You have to let me do it.
Oh. that's fine. You've made it
very clear that you're in command.
Here's what we'll do.
You worry about your team.
I'll worry about myself.
Cool it. Calm down. There's no fucking way
I'm letting you in there and you know it.
- Get the fuck off me!
- [dark music playing]
[man whistles]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Cédric.
You're emotional.
It's normal. but it's messing you up.
You're gonna have to trust me. okay?
Look at me.
We'll get every last hostage out of there.
safe and sound.
Okay?
- Yeah.
- If you're working with us. focus.
You're the one who knows the layout.
Can you focus? Can you keep it together?
I'm good.
So. let's go.
[music fades]
Get back to work. Show time's over. guys.
Witnesses report that several men.
all masked and heavily armed.
burst into the conservatory
at around 9:00 this morning
and took students hostage.
Police are already on the scene.
We have no further information yet
about what is clearly a major operation.
[man] We're waiting to hear
whether authorities set up
a direct line of communication
with the hostage takers
in order to begin negotiations.
So far the hostage takers
remain a mystery.
We don't know the group's name
or what they are demanding.
[indistinct chatter]
We have a chopper
hovering in this location.
but it can't stay there long.
We have to move fast.
I also sent out a drone.
We know that every entrance
is rigged with explosives.
With all these windows.
they can see us coming. Except here.
There's a blind spot in this building.
You see all the green here?
Those are telecommunications cables.
If we plug into them. we'll be able
to use all the security cameras.
- Is that the rest of the network?
- Yeah.
This is where we plug in.
which means we put the column here.
Valère. take whoever you need
from section 1.
Set up a tactical column there.
Okay. Can I have one of your guys
to hook me up to the cameras?
Yeah. sure. Uh. Rapha?
- Can you go with Valère?
- No problem.
- [Chloé] Take whatever gear you need.
- Okay.
[Chloé] I'll go back to tracking the van.
[indistinct chatter]
Cédric gave me the okay
to take part in the mission.
I'm really sorry about Manon.
She's my little sister.
We'll get her out of there. Don't worry.
Stay strong.
[poignant music playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
Yeah? Yeah. I'm coming. I'm on my way.
I'm not leaving. officer.
I've told you three times now.
You have to back up.
She's with me.
She's with me!
Okay.
Open up. Let her through. guys.
[dramatic music playing]
[Valère] Right. focus up.
Lock in. guys.
[dramatic music continues]
Move out.
[music fades]
My girl's here. so I'm here.
Jess. will you stay in the car?
Okay.
I'll be back.
With Manon.
I know.
[indistinct chatter]
[police siren blares in distance]
- [officer 1] Do you see the hostages?
- [officer 2] Negative. I do not.
[sighs]
[woman on radio] Family members
are just starting to arrive on the scene.
where a crisis team has been set up
to provide psychological support.
Clearly. the families are feeling shock…
[tense music playing]
[Valère] We just entered at door 3.
50 yards to the lobby.
[tense music continues]
[indistinct radio chatter]
How's it going. Cédric?
[Cédric] Should have access soon.
Pull up the images.
Valère?
- What's your status?
- [Valère] Entering the lobby.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Max] Backup in position.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Valère] We're in position.
- Okay.
- We're good.
[Rapha] Connecting.
[beeps]
- [Rapha] Link established.
- We're in.
Oscars and Tangos in the auditorium.
Three armed Tangos. Nine Oscars in hoods.
- Hostages bunched together.
- [Chloé] Check the other camera feeds.
- [gunshot]
- [grunts]
- [Valère] We're taking fire!
- [groans]
- [grunts and groans]
- [Max] Rapha!
[Valère] Two officers down.
I repeat. we have two officers down!
Valère. take cover! Everyone out of there!
Pull back. pull back!
- [Chloé] Shots fired!
- [Rapha groans]
[Valère] We got you. Rapha. okay?
[intense music playing]
[grunting]
- [gunshot]
- [screams]
[Cédric] We have shots fired!
[Max] You okay?
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
[David] It's gotta be
from the building next door. Cédric!
[Valère] We're evacuating.
we're evacuating.
Go on.
Schwepps. two pairs with me!
Valère. do you read me?
- [Max] Come on! Move!
- [Valère] You can make it! Keep going!
- [Valère] We're evacuating two wounded.
- Fuck!
[intense music continues]
[officer on comm] Confirmed.
we have shots fired next door.
[heavy gunfire]
[David] We're taking heavy fire
at the east entrance.
[screams]
[gunfire]
- [officer 1] Go. go. go!
- [officer 2] Move it!
[people screaming]
David. report position. Do you have cover?
- [David] We're in.
- Wait.
[Cédric] Secure your position.
I'm sending back up to you now.
- [indistinct shouting]
- [officer] Go. go!
[sirens blaring]
[Cédric] Reposition. north-west entrance.
Repeat. north-west.
[man on radio]
We just heard isolated gunshots
followed by bursts of automatic fire.
This could indicate that GIGN
is entering the building.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [man 1] GSW! Clear the way!
- [woman 1] I've got a crash cart!
[indistinct chatter]
[man 1] Support his pelvis. His pelvis.
They're loading them now.
- [woman 1] One. two. three.
- [man 1] Get him on the gurney.
- Okay. strap her in.
- [woman 1] Need oxygen!
[man 1] You're taking the second victim.
- [woman 1] Move out of the way.
- [man 1] You're gonna be fine.
[officer] If you need backup.
let me know right away.
[man 1] You good?
- Fine. that's it.
- [Max] We need you. Okay? You'll be fine.
Keep your eyes open. you'll be okay.
- [man 1] Let me know.
- [man 2] She was shot on the right side.
- [man 3] You'll be fine. Rapha.
- [woman 1] Come on!
[woman 2] Can you hear me. ma'am?
- [man 1] Give me the gauze pads.
- [man 2] Gauze.
Open your eyes. ma'am.
Squeeze my hand.
Ma'am. open your eyes.
Open your eyes if you can hear me.
- [man 2] Careful.
- [woman 2] Keep pressure.
You're with the paramedics.
Stay with us now. ma'am.
- [man 2] Eyes open.
- [woman 2] Open your eyes.
[woman 3] Open the gates.
[man 3] Moving in. let's go!
[intense music playing]
- [officer 1] Clear!
- [officer 2] Clear!
[David] Go!
Wait. Schwepps. Hang on. stop.
We're going up on the roof.
[man on radio] We're getting reports
that GIGN officers
have been injured in an exchange
of gunfire in the building.
[officer] Chloé. look at this camera feed.
We've got two more at the top.
[Chloé] Cédric. there's a total
of five Tangos in the auditorium.
There it is! I've got the van on a camera.
- It was at a self-storage yesterday.
- Okay. we're on it.
Rico. come here. take over for me.
[tense music playing]
[hostages whimpering]
Shut the fuck up!
[breathing heavily]
Cédric.
Terrorist's on the line.
She wants to talk to David.
- David?
- [David] Yeah. go ahead.
[Cédric] Terrorist on the line.
It's a woman.
Chloé and I are listening in.
She wants to talk to you.
[David] Okay. put her on.
- [Cédric] Connecting.
- [line chimes]
[Amal exhales slowly]
[static crackles]
[ominous music playing]
[Amal exhales slowly]
Surely you must know this is personal.
The GIGN took everything from me.
France took everything from me.
But you took my whole family.
My girl. my husband. my blood.
- I'll find your girl. I have a daughter.
- Save her.
Amal Mayard?
- [Amal] Commander Berger.
- Oh. shit.
[Amal] Like I said.
it's personal between you and me.
LAST FLOOR - FREIGHT ELEVATOR
I'm not here to negotiate. David.
I'm here today
to take everything from you.
And the whole world will be watching.
[closes phone]
[music darkens]
Oh. fuck.
In the army she specialized
in long-range shooting.
I'll take care of Amal.
Let's go. guys.
[Cédric] Tango leader
is on a suicide mission.
She's gonna execute the hostages.
We have to move in now.
- [police sirens blaring]
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [Valère] It's nothing.
- Lemme see your arm.
- Nothing to see.
- I have to check. It's my job.
See? It's nothing. It's just bullshit.
- Is he fit?
- Damn right I'm fit.
- [Cédric] Great. everyone in the Sherpa.
- Nice.
[suspenseful music playing]
- [elevator chimes]
- [doors open]
Guys! Guys! Listen up for a minute.
We're going into a building full of CL-20.
No matter what. we can't let them
detonate those explosives.
As you know. our motto is.
"A commitment to life. to all lives."
Unfortunately. there are situations
that call for hard choices.
So. Valère. Djibril. PJ. Nico. Max.
I'm going to need your sniper skills.
If we want to save the hostages.
we have to do some shooting.
It's the only way.
But you're only gonna get one shot.
So you better make sure it counts.
This is an operation
of the utmost delicacy.
Let's do a good job
so we all go home tonight. please.
- Alright. let's go! In the truck!
- [lively chatter]
- Gonna be okay. Valère?
- Totally.
- You got this. Demo?
- Hell yeah.
- [Cédric] Deal with the CL-20.
- All set to move. I'm sticking with Recon.
[Valère] Okay. guys. let's go.
- [tense music playing]
- [elevator chimes]
[Chloé] Yeah?
Chloé. on the cams for the music school.
can you see the targets go in?
[Chloé] Affirmative.
[David] And can you see them coming out?
Uh. negative.
Ah. fuck.
Somehow. they still fired at us
from the building next door.
so there has to be. uh…
[Chloé] An accomplice. maybe?
An underground passage.
Cédric. I'm dividing the team.
Okay. guys. let's switch up the plan.
We're looking for a tunnel. Schwepps.
You two go down that hallway.
We'll meet at the end.
Sergio. you guys take the third floor.
[Chloé] Okay. I'm 15 minutes out.
I'll call you from the warehouse.
[Cédric] Copy that. Sending in the Sherpa.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Max] Cédric?
Any news about Rapha?
She's in good hands.
Keep your head in the game. Max.
You know how it works.
If a teammate goes down.
step over them and keep moving.
If you can't handle it.
get off the truck now.
[Sherpa engine starts]
[dramatic music playing]
[music intensifies]
- [glass shatters]
- [music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Cédric] We just entered building B.
There's a man down in hallway S.
[Sergio] Team 1 proceeding
through hallway V. Nothing to report.
[Schwepps] Team 2 NSTR in hallway D.
[Cédric] We're crossing over
to building A.
[tense music continues]
Delta Echo Alpha Delta.
[Cédric] Separate columns.
Stop there!
[tense music continues]
Turn around nice and slow.
Put your weapon on the ground.
Hands on your head.
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[groans]
No!
That's not the plan.
[David groans]
[music fades]
I want him to live.
[David breathing heavily]
He's gonna see the whole thing.
He's gonna find out how it feels.
- [thuds]
- [grunts]
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[David] It's over.
You're surrounded.
Pretty soon.
you'll all be in cuffs or body bags.
It's over.
It isn't over until I say so.
[ominous music continues]
[grunts]
[men grunting]
[Valère] We're on the roof.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Rico] Still five terrorists
in the auditorium.
Three with the hostages.
Two at the top of the stairs.
[Valère] Snipers in position.
[Cédric] Okay.
Section 1.
we are go to enter the auditorium.
[suspenseful music continues]
[hostages whimpering]
[shaky breathing]
[magazine clicks into place]
[man] Shh. [tuts]
[Manon whimpers]
[officer 1] David. do you copy?
- [groans]
- [officer 1] We found him.
- David!
- [groans]
You okay?
I'm okay.
- [officer 1] Can you get up?
- Yeah.
- [officer 2] We're returning to hallway N.
- Thanks. [groans]
[squad chief] For the sniper shot.
it's countdown. then three seconds.
Snipers. when you're ready.
start the sequence.
[breathing nervously]
[Nico] One. ready.
[Djibril] Two. ready.
[Valère] Three. ready.
[PJ] Four. ready.
[Max] Five. no target.
[Cédric] Okay. Everyone hold on target.
Max. let us know when you're ready.
We start again on your go.
- [lock beeps]
- [door unlocks]
[suspenseful music continues]
[music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
[Max] Five is go for target.
[squad chief] Start the sequence.
[grunts]
[men grunting]
- [Nico] One. ready.
- [Djibril] Two. ready.
- [Valère] Three ready.
- [PJ] Four ready.
[Max] Five ready.
[squads chief] Countdown. Three seconds.
Three.
[simultaneous bullet hits]
[hostage pants]
- [Cédric] Deploy!
- [door opens]
- [officer 1] Show us your hands! Police!
- [officers shouting]
[officer 2] Don't move!
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[hostages whimpering]
[officer 2] Target one neutralized.
[officer 3] Target 2 neutralized.
Attention. priority alert. priority alert.
Two officers down in hallway S.
Amal is wounded. I'm in pursuit.
[Cédric] Five Tangos down. Confirmed.
Tanya. stay with me.
Everyone else. evacuate the hostages.
[Tanya] We've located
the rest of the CL-20.
[Cédric] Evacuating the hostages.
do you copy?
Evacuating the hostages.
Check their identity and then evacuate.
[hostages whimpering]
[Cédric] Tanya. how's it looking?
[Tanya] The last Oscar
is handcuffed to the device.
All the charges are wired to a timer.
It hasn't been activated.
The handcuffs could be rigged.
They're using a remote trigger.
[tense music continues]
[officer] Oscar 9. confirmed.
Oscar 4. Confirmed.
[Cédric] David. it looks like Amal
has a remote trigger on her.
[officer] Oscar 7. confirmed.
Oscar 8. confirmed.
[dramatic music playing]
[breathing shakily]
[David] Don't do it!
[Cédric] Hey. Manon.
It's Cédric. Everything's gonna be okay.
- [David] Put the gun down.
- [sniffles]
You haven't won. you know.
[dramatic music continues]
Say goodbye…
to your whole world.
- Now.
- [beeps]
- [gunshot]
- No!
[Tanya] The timer just started running.
We have five minutes.
We have to evacuate
the whole building right now.
[Cédric] All sections.
evacuate immediately.
Get the hostages out first.
I repeat. hostages first.
[officer] Copy that.
Evacuating hostages via building B.
Eight Oscars identified. no injuries.
[ominous music playing]
We don't have Oscar 3.
[officer] Let's get you out of here!
Follow the officers. hurry up! Come on.
Who is Oscar 3?
Who is Oscar 3?!
[Tanya] Cédric. tell him.
[Manon whimpers]
[Cédric] It's Manon.
[music intensifies]
Hey. Manon. It'll be fine.
You'll be all right. okay?
Just stay with me.
Breathe. breathe. Slow breaths.
[Tanya] There's something weird
about this setup.
I'm gonna install a jammer
and secure Manon.
Go for it.
Hey. guys!
Get out of here. please!
We have enough people. We'll handle it!
We'll handle it!
- Tanya. how much time?
- Four minutes.
You just never listen. do you?
Okay. focus. focus.
Eyes here. Breathe with me.
[suspenseful music playing]
Just got a hit.
Storage 237 belongs to Amal Mayard.
[Chloé] Okay. we're almost there.
- [tires squeal]
- [engines rev]
[officer] Getting there now.
I'm setting up the jammer.
[beeping]
[Cédric] Manon. you gotta trust me.
It's gonna be fine. Just hang in there.
[inhales deeply] Come on. It's okay.
- [Tanya] They connected something to you?
- [Manon] I don't know.
[Cédric] Don't look at that. Look at me.
[gasps]
Okay. it's fine.
[David panting]
Daddy.
You okay?
Yeah?
- How much time?
- 2:30.
Two minutes 30.
- What happened to you?
- Oh. you like the look?
Makes me look like a badass.
Should I keep it?
At one minute. we have to get out.
Get out. what does he mean?
All of us. Get out of here together.
that's what he means. Right. Cédric?
Besides. we're with the best here.
We have Tanya. You know her?
She's so good. Okay?
Y'know where she's from?
No? Nobody else does either.
Cédric. where's Tanya from?
[officer] Approaching the second floor.
Heading towards unit 237.
Max. you can go.
Get moving. now.
I'm not going anywhere.
[neon lights buzzing]
[officer] Clear.
There's no one here.
[Chloé] What the fuck?
Manon is clear to go.
Somebody get the bolt cutters.
- Okay.
- [Manon] What for?
- We're getting out. We're getting out.
- What for? What are we doing?
- We'll run.
- I don't want to run. I'm too tired.
- I can't do it!
- I'll carry you.
Tanya. what's the plan?
[Tanya] The jammer is powerful.
but we're not taking any risks.
We cut her free. and we run for it.
Got it. guys?
[Cédric] Go. go! Run. run. run!
[intense music playing]
[all panting]
[David grunting]
[Chloé] Shit.
she's the one who killed Kröller.
LINA MAYARD: A LIFE CUT SHORT
- [Cédric] Go. go!
- [Manon] Hey. Dad. it's okay.
- [David] What?
- Put me down.
Okay. Come on!
[panting]
[tense pensive music playing]
Fuck. no.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Chloé] David?
Where's Jess right now?
It's Jess.
Do you copy?
David.
It's Jess. Jess is the target.
[music intensifies]
David. do you copy?
[tense music builds]
[music stops]
[blast echoes]
[gasps]
[people screaming]
[beeping quickens]
[somber music playing]
[Manon sobs softly]
[music intensifies]
[somber music continues]
[dramatic music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm